#### Contact

soniarajsushanth@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dasararaju-sonia-3b095a174 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Yellow
Chatbot Testing
Chatbots

# Dasararaju Sonia

Chatbot Developer/Conversational AI | Microsoft Bot framework | Azure | LUIS | Cognitive services | Node js

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

## Summary

Experienced Chatbot Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the field of the information technology and services industry with an experience in developing Chatbots in different Bot frameworks like Microsoft Bot Framework, Dialogflow, Kore.Ai and also integrated bots with automation services like UiPath. Skilled in C#, Node js, Python, as well as HTML and Js and integrated bots with different channels like Teams, Webchat and also has an exposure of services by Azure and AWS.

## Experience

#### DAZN

Conversational Developer June 2023 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Tata Consultancy Services Chatbot Developer February 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 5 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Capgemini Chatbot Developer August 2019 - February 2022 (2 years 7 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Capgemini Invent Internship December 2018 - August 2019 (9 months) Hyderabad Area, India

### Education

# MVGR College of Engineering

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (June 2015 - June 2019)